1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
13. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
17. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
21. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
25. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/verify-succes-acount-login"))
33. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
37. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"))
41. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord("IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD", ENTER))
45. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-12 -pro"))
49. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product - IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD"))
53. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
57. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 7)
61. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
65. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn_checkout"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
69. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn_checkout"))
73. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Online Payment - Cradit Card"))
77. check(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkbox__I accept"))
81. click(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Checkout_Payment"))
85. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/Page Checkout/iframe_Credit Card"), 10)
89. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Page Checkout/iframe_Credit Card"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
93. delay(10)
97. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Page Checkout/field_cardNumber"), "5156 8399 3770 6777")
101. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Page Checkout/field_cardExp"), "01/30")
105. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Page Checkout/field_cvv2"), "993")
109. click(findTestObject("Checkout/btn-closed-pay"))
113. waitForAlert(10)
117. alertText = getAlertText()
121. comment(alertText)
125. acceptAlert()
129. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/track your order"), 7)
133. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/track your order"))
137. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/sp-order-list-item"))
141. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/btn-cencel"), 10)
145. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/btn-cencel"))
149. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/button_OK"), 7)
153. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/button_OK"))
157. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/Message_Success"), 10)
161. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/Message_Success"))
165. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/text_order_status"), 5)
169. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/text_order_status"), "CANCEL")
173. takeScreenshot()
177. closeBrowser()